

CONTACT ME AT



faratah@icloud.com



+359897070928



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ denislav-todorov-b65263205

SKILLS SUMMARY

•••• Creative

•••• Collaborative

•••• Positive attitude

•••• Tolerant

•••• Software Development

●●●● Process Improvement

DENISLAV TODOROV

BACKEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Currently studying at SoftUni and Veliko Tarnovo University. Worked on different projects utilizing various technologies. Love learning new skills and improving every day. Not afraid to do the research needed to increase my knowledge and abilities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER

Oct 2019- present

• Crypto Trading and Basic Graphic Design

Full-Stack Developer Internship

I PRIME HOLDING | June 2017 - Sept 2017

- SCRUM framework
- Git, Github
- C# .Net MVC
- Worked in a real environment
- MySQL, JS, HTML, CSS

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

SOFTUNI

C# Developer | June 2020 - till now

UNIVERSITY OF VELIKO TARNOVO

Software Engineering - Bachelor's degree | Oct 2016- till now

PMG AKAD. NIKOLA OBRESHKOV

Mathematics and information technologies | Sept 2010 - May 2016

CERTIFICATES

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/85248/c2566e35

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/96444/436fe6b3

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/104779/cccbe3ec